// English Grammer
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " What is C++?",
    answer: "C++ supports both procedural and object oriented programming language",
    options: [
      " C++ is an object oriented programming language",
      "C++ is a procedural programming language",
      "C++ supports both procedural and object oriented programming language",
      "C++ is a functional programming language"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is used for comments in C++?",
    answer: "both // comment or /* comment */",
    options: [
      "/* comment */",
      "// comment */",
      "// comment",
      "both // comment or /* comment */"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following user-defined header file extension used in c++?",
    answer: "h",
    options: [
      "h",
      "hg",
      "hf",
      "cpp"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is a correct identifier in C++?",
    answer: "VAR_1234",
    options: [
      "$var_name",
      "VAR_1234",
      "7var_name",
      "7VARNAME"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of Constructor in C++?",
    answer: "Friend constructor",
    options: [
      "Default constructor",
      "Parameterized constructor",
      "Copy constructor",
      "Friend constructor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following approach is used by C++?",
    answer: "Bottom-up",
    options: [
      "Left-right",
      "Bottom-up",
      "Right-left",
      "Top-down"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is virtual inheritance in C++?",
    answer: "C++ technique to avoid multiple copies of the base class into children/derived class",
    options: [
      "C++ technique to enhance multiple inheritance",
      "C++ technique to ensure that a private member of the base class can be accessed somehow",
      "C++ technique to avoid multiple inheritances of classes",
      "C++ technique to avoid multiple copies of the base class into children/derived class"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the difference between delete and delete[] in C++?",
    answer: "delete is used to delete single object whereas delete[] is used to multiple(array/pointer of) objects",
    options: [
      "delete is used to delete single object whereas delete[] is used to multiple(array/pointer of) objects",
      "delete is a keyword whereas delete[] is an identifier",
      "delete is used to delete normal objects whereas delete[] is used to pointer objects",
      "delete is syntactically correct but delete[] is wrong and hence will give an error if used in any case"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the size of wchar_t in C++?",
    answer: "Based on the number of bits in the system",
    options: [
      "2 or 4",
      "2",
      "4",
      "Based on the number of bits in the system"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which is more effective while calling the C++ functions?",
    answer: "call by reference",
    options: [
      "call by value",
      "call by reference",
      "call by pointer",
      "call by object"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "The C++ code which causes abnormal termination/behaviour of a program should be written under _________ block.",
    answer: "try",
    options: [
      "throw",
      "finally",
      "try",
      "catchc"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What is meant by a polymorphism in C++?",
    answer: "class having many forms",
    options: [
      "class having only single form",
      "class having four forms",
      "class having two forms",
      "class having many forms"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Pick the incorrect statement about inline functions in C++?",
    answer: "They are generally very large and complicated function",
    options: [
      "Saves overhead of a return call from a function",
      "They are generally very large and complicated function",
      "These functions are inserted/substituted at the point of call",
      "They reduce function call overheads"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What is abstract class in C++?",
    answer: "Class specifically used as a base class with atleast one pure virtual functions",
    options: [
      "Any Class in C++ is an abstract class",
      "Class from which any class is derived",
      "Class specifically used as a base class with atleast one virtual functions",
      "Class specifically used as a base class with atleast one pure virtual functions"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which concept allows you to reuse the written code in C++?",
    answer: "Inheritance",
    options: [
      "Inheritance",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction",
      "Encapsulation"
    ]
  },
];